[
    {
        "question": "Are you disabled?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "If you are disabled, Donald Trump was a nightmare to you. See below:",
         "url": "../images/disabled.gif"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you a reporter?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "If you are a reporter, Donald Trump was a mean grumpy scrooge to you. See below:",
        "url":"../images/disabled.gif"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you from Iowa?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Wow, didn't expect that. But yeah, Trump hates you too.",
        "url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PRUc11fPAwk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you Muslim?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Yeah, you're banned from the US if he gets in power. Sorry.",
        "url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MEewj5BJ9UI"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you a Seventh-day Adventist?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Oh. OK. But yeah Trump isn't a fan",
        "url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i2sb78ocimY"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you African American?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "This guy is ridiculous. He wants you bomb you",
        "url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k8TwRmX6zs4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you Asian?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "What a dick seriously. Donald Trump sucks. Here's what he had to say:",
        "url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1B8CvtA2Uvw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you a woman?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Donald Trump thinks that women have nothing to say. Here's an example:",
        "url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dDmb4pd3VNQ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you a Prisoner of War?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Donald Trump hates you and thinks your worthless and useless.",
        "url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oLWaoMCUg0g"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you someone who is not called 'Donald Trump'?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "text": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "text": "No"
            }
        ],
        "offended": 0,
        "feedback": "Yeah, at some point, Trump has offended you.",
        "url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a5wBY6D7V34"
    }
]